Jhal Hello Hello
Everyone Today our topic is about
both the health
insurance plans of Tata AIG which is
about the comparison of Medicare and Medicare Premier,
both are the health insurance
plans of Tata AIG, today we will explain to you what is the difference between these two products, if we
talk about village then in medical you
can select 5 lakh subscription appointment, free subscription 90
procedures both the products of
quality one day care procedure available
organ donor both the products have
Ghrit treatment which means that in any
such situation in which the policy holder
cannot visit the hospital,
then Ghrit is not available in the hospital, you can
take mid benefit in both the products, these
young girls both the products are
available in this the condition is that the
policy holder should be above 18
years of age and the one who is
above 40 should have it,
if the doctor comments that even if you have 409
you can restore these surgery benefits
Benefit: Both the
products are available. You have to keep in mind
that the coverage it gives for the same disease is Rs.
500. After this, you take global cover which
means that if you suffer from such a disease
which requires treatment outside India,
then you can get
your treatment done outside India in both the products. The
disease of this condition should be in India. For this
treatment, you can get Ayurvedic treatment done in both the
products. If we talk about ambulance, then
you can subscribe in Aa Medical,
whereas Yuva can avail hospitalization at Rs. 5000. If we
talk about constipation, then in Medicare you
can claim Rs. 52 per cent of minimum that
after 2 years, whereas Yuva you
can subscribe. You have to
open the setting in both the class products, and
both the products
are available. You have to keep in mind that you will get this
maximum, then that is the bill, you
can subscribe for more, if you have
taken this combination then 0.2 per cent of
subscription maximum  2010
that you can travel in your name from the company.
It means that in a situation
where the policy holder or any member is
admitted in the hospital for more than 5 days and none of
his family members is available there, in
case of any such situation the travel expenses of his family member
which you can afford can be up
to Rs 20000
which is available in both the products. Zoomable
benefits means that the benefits which they get are
not covered by any insurance company. This Cotton Club School is available in
both the products. No claim
bonus is available in both the companies.
Expedited rooms are available in both the products.
Sorry, if we talk about room rent then
you have to pay one percent. Medicare if
you have selected a plan with shared accommodation, there is no
such thing in the house.
Talking about direct lift then Medicare can be done
additionally whereas the appointment
is not available in Midcap Index whereas
in Medical Premier you can get Rs 50 thousand for baby after 4 years
and baby girl  You
can avail up to Rs 60,000 for this.
You can add it in the appointed decree.
Talking about post-vaccination, it
is not available in Medicare, whereas it
is available in Medicare Premier, which
you can avail up to Rs 1,000 for up to the age of 10 years. Roadways
Employees Action Benefit, which means
that if the policy holder or any member is
admitted in the hospital for more than 10 days, the additional benefit is availed. For
example, if you have a policy of
Rs 10 lakh 10 thousand, which is additional benefit of OPD
and Diagnostic, which means
that if
you get a test done for any disease diagnostic which is critical or
related to that kind, then you can avail up to Rs
25,000 for the tests you get done in the OPD as well.
We are
giving you the list of diseases on the screenshot, you
can easily see them, which is
not available in Medicare and
OPD treatment is available in Medicare Premier. Your
medical treatment is not available, whereas
Midcap is more  You can click on OPD up to ₹5000
friends today treatment medical and
dental treatment is not available that you can
apply for medical dental treatment
which you can use
for route Bhopal or for feeling
emergency air ambulance
is not available in comment whereas appointment you
can click on up to ₹5 among the products of Swayam Pimple Tata
AIG we hope
that this video will help you for free in
selecting the product please like
if you liked the video then
people keep bringing that information so please
like our channel and subscribe
thank you for watching